George Meany Center for Labor Studies Audio-visual Materials 6276 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
George Meany Center for Labor Studies Audio-visual Materials
1990-1997
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
George Meany Center for Labor Studies
6276 AV
3.44 cubic feet
3.1 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
8018768
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, April 09, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Collective bargaining -- Construction industry; Labor unions -- Organizing; George Meany Center for Labor Studies
8018768
- Winter 1994 (Box 1)
- Summer 1994 (Box 2)
- Spring 1994 (Box 3)
- Winter 1993 (Box 4)
- Winter 1993 (Box 5)
- Fall 1993 (Box 6)
- Summer 1993 (Box 7)
- Summer 1993 (Box 8)
- Spring 1993 (Box 9)
- Spring 1993 (Box 10)
- Winter 1992 (Box 11)
- Fall 1992 (Box 12)
- Summer 1992 (Box 13)
- Summer 1992 (Box 14)
- Spring 1992 (Box 15)
- Volume One - 1990 (Box 16)
- Volume One 1990 (Box 17)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Volume 1 - 1997 (Box 18)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Volume III - 1996-1997 (Box 19)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Volume III - 1996-1997 (Box 20)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Premier Edition (Box 21)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Premier Edition (Box 22)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Premier Edition (Box 23)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Premier Edition (Box 24)
- On Target An Audio Magazine - Premier Edition (Box 25)
- Labor Law and the Construction Industry (Box 26)
- Organizing in the Construction Industry (Box 27)
- Collective Bargaining in the Construction Industry (Box 28)